<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <FTND_NuclearFlare.label>electromagnetic pulse</FTND_NuclearFlare.label>
  <FTND_NuclearFlare.description>A Nuclear electromagnetic pulse occurs in the area. The electromagnetic interference will prevent most electrical devices from working.</FTND_NuclearFlare.description>
  <FTND_NuclearFlare.endMessage>The electromagnetic pulse is ending.</FTND_NuclearFlare.endMessage>
  <FTND_NuclearFlare.letterText>A Nuclear electromagnetic pulse has occured.\n\nThe intense radiation will shut down all electrical devices.\n\nIt should pass in about a day.</FTND_NuclearFlare.letterText>

  <FTND_NuclearFallout.label>nuclear fallout</FTND_NuclearFallout.label>
  <FTND_NuclearFallout.description>A plume of radioactive fallout is slowly settling over this entire region. Any living thing not under a roof will be slowly poisoned, and items left outside will corrode.</FTND_NuclearFallout.description>
  <FTND_NuclearFallout.endMessage>The worst of the toxic fallout has settled.</FTND_NuclearFallout.endMessage>
  <FTND_NuclearFallout.letterText>A plume of radioactive fallout is settling over this entire region.\n\nAny person or creature not under a roof will be slowly sickened by the toxic dust settling out of the atmosphere.\n\nIt will last for anywhere between a few days to over a quadrum.</FTND_NuclearFallout.letterText>

  <FTND_NuclearWinter.label>nuclear winter</FTND_NuclearWinter.label>
  <FTND_NuclearWinter.description>A nuclear explosion has occurred and massive quantities of ash have spewed into the atmosphere., significantly reducing the amount of light which reaches the surface. Temperatures will be colder and plants will grow slower.</FTND_NuclearWinter.description>
  <FTND_NuclearWinter.endMessage>Most of the ash has settled.</FTND_NuclearWinter.endMessage>
  <FTND_NuclearWinter.letterText>A nuclear explosion has occurred and massive quantities of ash have spewed into the atmosphere..\n\nAsh in the atmosphere will obscure the sun. Temperatures will drop and plants will suffer for lack of sunlight. It could pass in a few weeks, or it might last many quadrums.</FTND_NuclearWinter.letterText>

  <FTND_Flashstorm.label>electromagnetic storm</FTND_Flashstorm.label>
  <FTND_Flashstorm.description>A freak localized storm is blasting a small area with repeated lightning strikes.</FTND_Flashstorm.description>
  <FTND_Flashstorm.endMessage>The electromagnetic storm is over.</FTND_Flashstorm.endMessage>
  <FTND_Flashstorm.letterText>A freak localized flashstorm is striking a small area with lightning. This can cause massive fires.</FTND_Flashstorm.letterText>


</LanguageData>